<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<!DOCTYPE sect1 PUBLIC "-//OASIS//DTD DocBook XML V4.5//EN"
  "http://www.oasis-open.org/docbook/xml/4.5/docbookx.dtd" [
  <!ENTITY % general-entities SYSTEM "../../general.ent">
  %general-entities;
]>
<sect1 id="pre-organization">
  <?dbhtml filename="organization.html"?>

  <title>Structure</title>

  <para>This book is divided into the following parts.</para>

  <sect2>
    <title>Part I - Introduction</title>

    <para>Part I explains a few important notes on how to proceed with the
    Cross-LFS installation. This section also provides meta-information about
    the book.</para>

  </sect2>

  <sect2>
    <title>Part II - Preparing for the Build</title>

    <para>Part II describes how to prepare for the building
    process including downloading the packages.</para>

  </sect2>

  <sect2>
    <title>Part III - Make the Cross-Compile Tools</title>

    <para>Part III shows you how to make a set of Cross-Compiler
    tools. These tools can run on your host system but allow you to
    build packages that will run on your target system.</para>

  </sect2>

  <sect2>
    <title>Part IV - Building the ELFS System</title>

    <para>Part IV shows you how to build the core ELFS system.  Compiling
    and installing Buxybox and other required packages, making the system
    bootable, setting up the bootscripts, and installing a bootloader.</para>

  </sect2>

  <sect2>
    <title>Part V - Cleanup and Boot</title>

    <para>Part V provides instructions on creating a root file system using compiled packages.</para>

  </sect2>

    <sect2>
    <title>Part VI - Supporting Beyond Linux From Scratch (BLFS) </title>

    <para>Part VI  provides instructions on extending the system so as to make use of BLFS.</para>

  </sect2>



  <sect2>
    <title>Appendices</title>

    <para>The appendices contain information that doesn't really fit anywhere
    else in the book. Appendix A contains definitions of acronyms and
    terms used in the book; Appendix B gives acknowledgments to people
    who have helped work on the ELFS project and website; Appendix C and
    D have information about package dependencies and the the build
    order; Appendix E provides the Open Publication License.</para>

  </sect2>

</sect1>
